麦克斯  卡洛琳
Max, Caroline.
是阿憨拿着迷你iPad走过来
Look, here comes Han carrying an iPad mini.
还是iPad拿着一只迷你阿憨而来啊
Or is it an iPad carrying a mini Han?
阿憨居然有迷你iPad
Han has a mini iPad?
我们连大号卫生巾都买不起
We can't even afford a Maxi pad.
好不爽  我说谎坑[困]死自己了
I am so upset. I'm stuck in a lie.
那也好过你上次
Well, it's better than the time
把自己困在背包里啊
you got stuck in that backpack.
别闹了  我有麻烦了
Seriously, you guys. I'm in trouble.
我刚看到邮件
I just opened this email,
我妈要来看我
and my mother is coming to visit.
原来你有妈妈啊
You have a mother?
我还以为你的诞生
I thought you came to life
是因为玩具店里某个小孩许了个愿
after a kid in a toy store made a wish.
阿憨  你妈妈千里迢迢从韩国来看你
Han, your mother's coming all the way from Korea to see you.
这不是该高兴吗
Isn't that great news?
我这脸看起来像高兴吗
Is this the face of great news?
重点是  我妈以为我有个女朋友
See, my mother thinks I have a girlfriend.
我爸也以为我朋友
My father still thinks I wasn't in the car
在度假地撞死骗子的时候  我不在场啊
when my friend hit that grifter in the Hamptons.
她以为我有个女朋友
She thinks I have a girlfriend
是因为我貌似有说过这话
because I might have told her I did.
你是说过还是没说过
Did you or didn't you?
貌似有
I-I might have.
我貌似也有发了一个女人的照片给我妈
And I might have sent my mother pictures of someone
跟她说那就是我女朋友
and told her that she was the woman I'm dating.
阿憨  你"鲶鱼"了你妈吗
Han, you might have catfished your mom?
貌似是吧
I might have.
鲶鱼嘛  我懂
Catfishing-- right.
就是指在酒吧钓上了个妞
That's when you pick up a woman in a bar,
等带她到灯光明亮的地方时
and when you get her in the light,
才发现她有长胡须
you realize she has whiskers.
对了  爷照"上"不误
P.S.-- doesn't bother me.
"鲶鱼"是指在网上伪装成别人
No, catfishing is when you pretend to be someone
隐藏真实的自己
you're not on the internet.
基本网上的人都那样
You know, like everyone on the internet.
我妈唯一的心愿就是我有一段
All my mother wants is for me to be happily married
她跟我爸一样的美满姻缘
like my father and her.
我妈唯一的心愿就是能治愈丙型肝炎
All my mother wants is a cure for hep-c.
我发了她的照片
Look, here she is.
"韩国美女金君恩  艺名蓝宝石"
"Korean beauty June Kim, aka Sapphire"?
阿憨  你居然找了个妓女
Han, you chose a prostitute?
她才不是妓女  只是有个人网站而已嘛
She's not a prostitute. She has a website.
我还认识个男的  名片上写着
Yeah, and I know a guy with business cards
专业"菊花放松师"呢
whose "job" it is to relax your rectum.
上面写她在曼哈顿的
It says she's an exotic dancer
一家男士夜总会里当脱衣舞女
at this gentlemen's club in Manhattan.
那你就去那请这位妓女
So just go there and hire the hooker
来当你女朋友就好啦
to pretend to be your girlfriend.
我从没想过我会说出这句话
And there's a sentence I never thought I'd say.
我试过了  但门卫让我去巷子里等妈妈来
I tried, but the bouncer told me to wait in the alley
像其他没大人领着进酒吧小孩一样
for my mother like all the other children.
所以我想麻烦你们帮我跑一趟
So I was hoping you guys could go for me.
阿憨  我们不会帮你的
Han, we are not doing that.
脱衣酒吧  谎言  太掉我的价了
Strip clubs, lies-- that's not my scene.
太掉你的"价"
That's not your "scene"?
你还有个价吗
You have a scene?
符合你价的情景是怎样啊
What is your scene, Caroline?
我好像还没见过啊
I haven't seen your scene.
你自己都两年没见过你符合你价的场景了
In fact, you haven't seen your scene in two years.
听姐的  这情景就是你现在的价
Trust me, this is your scene now.
行  我明白了
Oh, I understand.
我就问一件事
Just one question--
我到底有没有
Did I or did I not let you have
免你们小蛋糕窗口的租金呢
the cupcake window rent-free?
靠  阿憨  你这招够狠啊
Wow, Han. That's a cheap shot.
又损又贱  敬佩敬佩
Low, bitchy-- I respect that.
我们帮你去脱衣酒吧
We'll go to the strip club,
但如果里面都是  脱脱脱
But if it's nude, nude, nude,
我绝对走走走
I am leaving, leaving, leaving.
这绝对是阿憨生平首次
That's the first time Han's ever been able
把东西举过别人头上啊
to hold something over someone's head.
姑娘们  蓝宝石马上就来
Sapphire will be right with you, ladies.
谢谢了  老大哥
Thank you, my good man.
拿张阿憨给的20块给我
Give me a 20 from Han.
这里绝对得给小费  不然会被人砍死的
You gotta tip at these places or they'll murder you.
谢了  美女
Thanks, doll.
你们两位可以坐在沙发上稍待片刻
You'se twos can have a seat on that couch.
不  不用了  谢谢
Oh, no. No, Thank you.
我今天...
I'm not catching--
可不想染上"梅  淋  肝"...
not catching "Sypha-gonna-titus" today.
全世界最适合洗"妓女澡"的地方
Well, if a whore's bath is appropriate anywhere,
就是这里了吧
it's here.
麦克斯  人家进来后  请以专业眼光看待
Max, please be professional when she comes in.
不许乱开黄腔
No sexual comments.
凭她每天一进来就得面对
Considering she's used to walking in on dudes
手上握着鸡鸡  好像那是礼物似的男人
who have their junk in their hand like a sad present,
我肯定不会做出让她不爽的事
I am sure I can manage to not offend her.
我的意思是  要记得无论工作场地为何
I'm just saying that despite where we are, let's remember,
她与我们一样都是商场英雌
she's a business woman like us.
董事会主席已经到位
The chairman of the board is here.
女士们  准备好要爽一把了吗
Hi, ladies. You ready for a good time?
等一辈子了
Been waitin' my whole life.
你好  很高兴见到你
Hello. It's a pleasure to meet you.
我是卡洛琳·钱宁
I'm Caroline Channing,
她是我的同事  麦克斯·布莱克
and this is my colleague, Max Black.
所以今天怎么搞  我不能一次服务两人
Yo, how's this gonna work? I don't do two at a time.
你们俩谁想看  谁想"骑"
So who wants to watch, who wants to ride?
这样吗
Oh, right.
基本上我们两个都不"骑"
Neither of us will be riding, per se.
妹儿  话先别说太早
Hold your roll, girl.
咱们砸了阿憨不少钱进来的呢
We're spending a lot of Han's money here.
姐姐若是想要骑  就得骑
If I want a ride, I'm getting a ride.
该称呼你君恩还是蓝宝石呢
Um, is it June or Sapphire?
只要你给钱  叫我保罗都行
You can call me Paul if you pay me.
君恩  我们不是来看大腿舞
June, we're not here for a dance
或来享受你其他我完全没意见的服务
or any of the other things you do that I don't judge you for
我思想很前卫哦
because I'm very open-minded.
我去过阿姆斯特丹红灯区
I've been to Amsterdam.
这里有监视器在看  我必须得跳舞
I'm on camera so I gotta dance for someone
不然我老板会炒了我
or my bosses will fire me.
然后就得回到女服务员生活
And then it's back to waiting tables.
我答应过自己不会再堕落到那地步
told myself I'd never sink that low again.
我们每天换上制服前也这么对自己说
Yeah, we say that every day when we get dressed for work.
坐下  我们开始吧
Okay, sit. Let's do this.
没事  我应该都先擦干净了
It's fine. I think I got all the stains.
我们现在正式还清欠阿憨的人情了
It's official! We've paid Han back.
能麻烦你换另一种灯光吗
Um, could you turn the other lights on?
她对事实过敏
She's allergic to the truth.
君恩  是这样的  我们的老板...
So, June, here's the thing. We have this boss.
小妞  使劲接着跳
Yeah, girl, work that.
我是在给她鼓励  职场女性互相勉励啊
I'm being encouraging, businesswoman to businesswoman.
言归正传  他叫李憨
Anyway, his name is Han Lee, and see,
他母亲要来探望他
his mother is coming to visit.
这招棒啊
Oh, nice move there.
不不不不  我不是激励你过来
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I wasn't encouraging.
纯评论而已
Just commenting.
哎哟妈呀  你的头出现了
Oh, peek-a-boo, there's your head.
总之他妈希望他找个女朋友
Anyway, he needs a girlfriend,
所以他就发了你照片给他妈
so he sent his mother pictures of you
然后说你是他女朋友
and said you were his girlfriend.
轮到她了吧
I think it's her turn.
今天来目的就是
Oh, uh-- the gist is,
他愿意付你钱  请你假扮他女朋友
he's willing to pay you to pretend to be his girlfriend.
我也愿意付你钱  请你教我
And I'm willing to pay you to show me
怎么用我的丰臀使出这招
how to do that with my hips.
你绝对能当个好脱衣舞娘啊
Ooh, you would make a great stripper.
我知道  我只是害怕成功
I know, I just have a fear of success thing.
我们能先关上音乐吗
Can we turn the music off?
我开始有点晕头转向了
'Cause I'm getting disoriented
而且老实说  还有点性奋
and, in all honesty, a little turned on.
但我现在事情已经够多
And I cannot be a latent bisexual
实在不是个变疑似双性恋的好时机
with everything else already on my plate.
你们出多少钱
How much?
我们付你跟人上床的费用
Whatever your rate is for sex,
但你都不用出卖身体
but you won't even have to have sex.
顶多就是亲亲小嘴
At the most, just kissing.
-亲嘴要收费五百  -我爱你
- Kissing is $500. - I love you.
我可以给他来个女友体验套餐
Okay. I can give him the "girlfriend experience" package.
他没女友  没经验[体验]  更没大雕[套餐]
He has no girlfriend, no experience, and no package,
这真是太适合了
so that sounds perfect.
拿去  厄尔  等我妈进来
Here, Earl, when my mother comes in,
你就假装在读这个
pretend you are reading this.
传说中的圣经啊
Ooh, the Bible.
我还记得这书刚上市那会呢
You know, I remember when this first came out.
压根没料到会变得这么火
Didn't think it would be a hit.
我的老天  厄尔别拿我们的主开玩笑
Earl, we're talking about our lord, Jesus Christ!
还没有"妈妈  妈妈大人  妈妈憨"的影子吗
So, no sign of mama-say-mama-sah-ma-mama-Han?
不知道  我不知道她长什么样
I don't know. I don't know what she looks like.
她来了
She's here.
阿憨
Han!
我不知道憨妈是缩小版阿憨
I can't tell if she's a smaller him
还是阿憨是年轻版憨妈
or if he's a smaller her.
这里是威廉斯堡餐厅
여기 는 Williamsburg diner 에요
您一定是阿憨的妈妈
You must be Han's mother.
我是厄尔
I'm Earl.
我刚刚还在读圣经呢
I was just reading the Bible,
因为我无时无刻都在读啊
'cause when am I not?
母亲大人  这位是卡洛琳
Mother, this is Caroline.
嘿哟
Hay-yo!
卡洛琳  我都不知道你会说韩语
Caroline, I didn't know you spoke Korean.
在我彻底掌握日语后  学了韩语当选修
I took it as an elective after I mastered Japanese.
当年有个预感  有天亚洲会一统世界
I had a hunch Asia was gonna take over the world.
恭喜恭喜  我没猜错
And congratulations, right on track.
卡洛琳  你的韩语说得很好
Caroline, your Korean is very good.
这位是麦克斯
And this is Max.
幸会幸会  李女士
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Lee.
那表情在韩语里代表啥意思
What does that face mean in Korean?
表示你该把上衣拉链拉上
It means zip up your top.
来  母亲  请坐  您一定饿了
Here, mother, sit. You must be hungry.
我去给你拿菜单
I'll get you a menu.
奇了怪了
That's weird.
这对宝贝从来都是给人们带来欢乐啊
These usually bring joy to the people.
李憨  你的女朋友呢
Han Lee, where is your girlfriend?
明晚吃饭就能见到了
You'll meet her at dinner tomorrow.
她也想来
She wanted to be here,
但她要去教会  还要帮人做脑部手术
but with church and all her work in brain surgery,
她实在抽不开身
she's very busy.
在你说你的女友
And I thought it was unrealistic
不是"充气的"时我就觉得假  没想到你还...
when you had a girlfriend that didn't need an air pump.
阿憨  你想什么呢
Han, what are you thinking?
你要怎么去圆这个谎
How are you ever going to pull this off?
靠我两位死党的大力帮忙啊
With the help of my two best friends?
那挺好啊  他们是谁
Oh, good. Who are they?
拜托了  约君恩去你们家
Please, have June come to your apartment
我们先跟她对台词[快]
and we can brief her.
跟你"一起"  肯定"快"啊
Well, if it's with you, it's gonna be brief.
-别忘了  你们欠我的  -才不是  阿憨
- Remember, you owe me. - No, Han.
在酒吧  我看见一面感觉会怀孕的墙
At that club, I saw a pregnant wall.
所以...
So...
人情债已经两清了
I think we're even.
我是来见君恩的  为什么要蒙我眼睛
If I'm here to meet June, why am I blindfolded?
这样你就不会知道我们到底住哪儿
So you can never find your way back to our apartment again.
但工作表上有填你们的住址啊
But I have your address on your work forms.
会填这里才怪
No, you don't.
麦克斯  我觉得可以把眼罩摘下了
Max, I think he can take it off now.
都蒙了一个小时了
It's been an hour,
而且我们还带他绕了三圈
and we spun him around three times.
看来我是到跳蚤市场了
Well, someone's been to a flea market.
这里闻起来有一股大麻味
And it smells like pot in here.
人家上班前抽了一点而已啦  没办法
So I smoked up a little before work. I got to.
谁让我老板是个烦人精
My boss is a real butt munch.
我们的应召女郎到啦
Okay, our call girl is here.
我也从未想过我会说这句话
Another sentence I never thought I'd say.
我看起来像打电话叫过小姐的人  对吧
I look like I've had a call girl before, right?
阿憨  你看起来就像从没给女人打电话的人
Han, you don't look like you've called a girl before.
我得平静下来
I need to calm down.
你这有甘菊茶吗
Do you have any chamomile tea?
没有  我又不是那种在秋风中
No, because I'm not a divorced woman
呆坐在阳台的离异妇女
on a balcony in the fall.
但我的确有东西能帮你放松
But I do have something that will help you relax.
你是说[大麻]
Ooh, you mean--
是的  我要用一个看不见的小口哨哄你入睡
Yes, I'm gonna lull you to sleep with a tiny, invisible whistle.
君恩  你干这行是为了要赚学费
So, June, are you working your way through
还是有难言之隐
graduate school or something?
都不是  我喜欢做爱有钱赚
No, I like getting paid for sex.
你不觉得时不时就有钱交我那套
I mean, what's a handy every now and then if it pays
全景阳台豪华公寓的按揭  不是很方便吗
the mortgage on my Parkview Terrace apartment, right?
生活有时真的很有意思
Life is so funny sometimes.
正当你窃喜自己比别人好时
Just when you think you're better than someone,
却惊觉其实不然
you're not.
我们好了  整个人都放松了
Here we are, all relaxed.
刚才真是疯狂
And that was wild,
感觉就像小仓鼠抽大麻抽嗨了
like getting your hamster stoned.
君恩  这些是阿憨告诉他妈妈
Okay, June, this has all the details
有关你的所有细节
that Han sent his mom about you.
你告诉你妈我是一个哈佛毕业的基督徒医生
You told your mom I'm a Harvard-educated Christian doctor
还是一个有名的古典乐钢琴家
and also a renowned classical pianist?
对  我们在教堂相遇  然后疯狂爱上对方
Yes, we met at church and are crazy in love,
但我们都遵守戒律  不结婚不上床
but we're waiting till marriage.
好吧  处女服务要一千
Oh, well, the virgin experience is 1,000.
八百行吗
Will you take 800?
-麦克斯  -干嘛
- Max! - What?
我失身的时候不省人事
I was unconscious when I lost mine.
我也想见识一下是怎样
And I want to see what it's like.
希望是披萨来了
Oh, I hope that's pizza.
因为现在我够胆
'cause I could go to third base
跟面包团[胸部]来个亲密接触
on some crazy bread right now.
不  是苏菲啦
No! It's Sophie.
我让她带几条十字项链给君恩
I asked her to bring down some crosses
好让她见你妈妈时戴上
for June to wear when she meets your mom.
什么  苏菲也知道我请妓女
What? Sophie knows I hired a prostitute
来当我的女友吗
to be my girlfriend?
没有啦  我什么都没说
No, I didn't tell her anything.
但这是一个测试的好机会
But this will be a good test to see
看看别人会不会觉得你们是一对
if you two pass as a couple.
阿憨跟那个妓女坐在一起干嘛
Hey, what's Han doing with that hooker?
苏菲  这位是君恩
Sophie, this is June.
阿憨的妈妈来了  所以我们请她
We hired her to pretend to be Han's girlfriend
来假扮阿憨的女朋友
while his mom's in town.
慢着  所以他妈妈
Oh, wait, so his mom
会真的相信
is supposed to believe that
他们的某部位"合"上了
their parts match up somehow
而且她还感觉很爽吗
and that's a fun thing for her?
笑死姐了
Oh. L-O-L.
这事就属于那种
Oh, this is one of those things
过了一会想起来  还是会忍俊不禁的类型
that you think about later and you laugh.
对了  卡洛琳  瞧
Look, look, Caroline, look.
我把十字项链拿来了
I brought you your crosses.
苏菲  你就没有小点的吗
Sophie, do you have anything smaller?
这是约会  不是搞驱魔
It's a date, not an exorcism.
好吧  谁让你不早点说
Oh, well, you gotta say that.
好吧  我马上回来
All right, I'll be right back.
瞧  过了一会  我想起来还是笑死姐了
You see, I'm thinking about it later and I'm L-O-L'ing.
我得走了  这事妥了
Well, I gotta go. I got this.
但这材料有很多呢
But that's a lot of material.
你不打算留下来  死记硬背一下吗
You don't want to stay and cram it?
这又要多少钱
How much for that?
不要钱  没关系  我超会装的
No, it's cool. I can fake it.
你确定你可以吗
You're sure you can fake it?
那你们来评评看
Can I fake it?
天啊  天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
好爽  好爽  爽死了
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
装得一脸好高潮啊
She's sure.
怎么阿憨跟他女朋友还不来
I wonder why Han and his girlfriend are late?
或许临时有事
Maybe something came up
他女朋友得处理一下
and she had to take care of it.
其实  可能  就是这样
That's actually probably exactly what happened.
希望我的头发看起来还行
I hope my hair looks all right.
因为我今天把假发反过来戴
I'm wearing it the other way.
看起来很漂亮
It looks pretty.
是啊  完全看不出来
Yes. Very pretty.
我的小憨憨终于找到了
I am just so excited that my Han
完美的另一半  我好兴奋
finally found the perfect girlfriend.
他的君恩是一位优秀的脑外科医生
Oh, you know, his June is a brilliant brain surgeon.
她的确非常了解各种"头"部
Well, she certainly knows a lot about head.
她每个周日都会去教堂
And she also goes to church every Sunday.
是啊  她总是"跪在地上"[口交]
Yep, that girl is always on her knees.
她还是位古典乐钢琴家[阴茎玩家]
And she is a classical pianist.
她这些话真是槽点满满
She is making this too easy.
他们来了
Oh, there they are.
阿憨  阿憨
Han! Han!
还有阿憨的女朋友
And girlfriend of Han.
母亲大人  这位是君恩
Mother, may I present June?
君恩  这是我妈  李素敏
June, this is my mother, Su-min Lee.
你就叫我李素敏行啦
Please, call me Su-min Lee.
"素敏"的谐音就是态度差
Which means, so mean to me.
很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
一直以来  久仰大名
I've heard such a great deal about you.
阿憨也跟我说了你们相遇的经过
Oh, and Han has told me how you two met.
真是个美丽的故事
What a beautiful story.
没错
Oh, yes.
的确很美  我们是在
That was beautiful when we met at...
楼上  屋顶
Upstairs on the roof--
是教堂  我们在教堂相遇的
Church! We met in church.
教堂楼上的屋顶
Upstairs on the roof of church.
我们想离上帝更近一点
We wanted to be closer to God.
我们俩都是虔诚的信徒
We are both so holy!
这里是不是很热啊  还是因为现在这情况
Is it hot in here? Or is it just the situation?
瞧  李女士花钱点的
Oh, look, the appetizers Mrs. Lee
开胃菜上桌啦
is paying for are here.
在我们开始吃开胃菜前
Before we start on the appetizers,
金恩  要先祷告
June, please pray.
我不懂祷告时要说什么
I don't know any prayers.
不用  我来吧  母亲大人
No, no, I'll do it, mother.
但首先  我能来杯莫斯科骡子鸡尾酒吗
But first please, can I get a Moscow mule?
来嘛  金恩  快祷告
Go, June. Please, pray.
上帝啊[爽啊]
Oh, God.
上帝啊  上帝啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
上帝啊  上帝啊  上帝啊
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
阿门
And amen!
好吧
Oh, okay.
我还不知道有这种呢
I-I don't know that one.
我快饿死了
Hey. I am starving.
真是天赋异禀
That's quality.
你胃口真好  一整根直接吞下去了[深喉口交]
Such a good appetite. You ate the whole thing.
都不用牙
Didn't even chew.
君恩  现在没人弹钢琴了
June, the piano is free.
你来为我们弹奏一曲吧
Oh, you must play something for us.
不  她不能弹
No, she can't play.
但你跟我说她能啊
Yeah, but you told me that she was--
我是说现在
I mean, now.
她总不能现在跑去弹钢琴吧
I mean, she can't play the piano now.
瞧  李女士
Look, look, Mrs. Lee.
快看克莱斯勒大厦
The chrysler building.
上面有"克莱斯"[耶稣]几个字呢
It has the word "Chris" in it.
阿憨  你的餐刀掉了
Hey, Han, you dropped your knife.
你最好冷静一点  不然会穿帮的
You better calm down. You're gonna blow it.
穿帮的[口交]代价你可付不起
You can't afford to blow it.
你连接吻的钱都付不起
You can't even afford to kiss it.
我又开始紧张了
I'm getting tense all over again.
快帮兄弟一把
Help a brother out.
你觉得我会把那玩意放在我手包里
What, you think I just carry that stuff around with me
装在一个外面贴有独角兽贴纸的
in my purse in an Altoids container
薄荷糖盒子里  随身带着吗
with a lisa frank unicorn sticker on it?
麦克斯  接下来该怎么办
Max, what is going to happen?
我有一个更想知道的问题
I've got a more pressing question--
一个人的嘴巴这么小
How does someone with a mouth so small
怎么会把烟卷弄这么湿呢
get a joint so wet?
一旦知道君恩不会弹钢琴
When June cannot play the piano,
我妈就会发现我在撒谎
mother will discover my lie.
她肯定会非常非常失望
It will be a big, big disappointment.
我可是我们家的荣耀啊
I am the star of my family.
也就是说如果你们家是杰克逊家族的话
So, if your family were the Jacksons,
那你就是迈克·杰克逊吗
You'd be Michael?
我觉得你的身形更像提托
'cause I see you more as a Tito.
老实说  应该是娇小版的
Actually, petite-o.
阿憨的妈妈就跟在我后面
Han's mom is right behind me.
她看见你们俩进来了
She saw you two come in here.
我试图阻止过她
I tried to stop her,
但她力气好大  动力十足啊
but she has strength, and it is all core.
阿憨  快躲起来
Han, hide.
我直冒冷汗  都把标价签给弄湿了
I'm sweating through the price tag.
这身衣服我还得还回去呢
And I have to return this.
如果这次失败了
If I'm going down,
我也要爽着失败
I'm going down high.
光是接吻的价格是五百块
It's 500 for kissing.
你可付不起往"下"这份钱
You can't afford to go down.
你跟我的小憨憨是怎么回事
What is going on between you and my Han?
你们俩整晚都在说悄悄话
You two have been whispering all night.
可怜的君恩啊
Poor June.
可怜[穷]的君恩
Poor June?
可怜的君恩住的可是有保安的豪华公寓
Poor June lives in a doorman building.
李女士  我觉得你对麦克斯的印象
Mrs. Lee, I think you might have gotten
可能有点偏差
the wrong impression of Max.
不  她追我儿子
No, she is after my son
就是想得到他那家成功的餐馆
for his big successful diner.
你还有另一个儿子吗
Oh, you have another son?
我看穿你了
I am on to you.
你就是一个拜金爱钱
You are just a money-grubbing,
胸大淫荡的下流女
Big-booby, dirty nasty girl.
我也想说你说错了  但的确是啊
Well, I wish I could say you were wrong.
母亲大人  别说了
Mother, stop!
你不能这么跟麦克斯说话
You cannot talk to Max like that.
她是个好女孩  好朋友
She is a good girl, and a friend, and--
什么
Wha?
好吧  被你逮个正着
Okay, yes, you caught me.
我抽大麻
I smoke weed.
没错  跟你担心的一样
Yes, I'm living the fast life
我在纽约过着快节奏的生活
in New York city just as you feared.
什么
Wha?
但我只有在
But I only toke up
压力很大的情况下才抽一口
when I am under a lot of pressure.
母亲大人
See, mother,
其实我没有女朋友
I don't have a girlfriend.
君恩是我花钱请来的妓女
June is a prostitute I paid to pretend,
好让你觉得我们跟你和爸爸一样幸福
so you would think we were happy as you and father.
把那玩意给我
Give me that.
什么
Wha?
我的压力也很大  儿子
I too am under a lot of pressure, son.
其实我和你父亲已经分开了
The truth is your father and I are no longer together.
他跟别的女人偷情
He had an affair with another woman
那女的咪咪就跟她的一样假
who has big fake ones like her.
麦克斯的咪咪是纯天然的哦  李女士
Max's breasts are real, Mrs. Lee.
上帝厚爱你啊
God bless.
如果你想知道的话  我的也是哦
Mine are too, in case you were wondering.
我不想知道
I wasn't.
儿子  你对我失望吗
Son, are you disappointed in me?
母亲大人  你对我失望吗
Mother, are you disappointed in me?
不  阿憨
No, Han.
你是我们家族和我心里的荣耀
You are the star of our family and my heart.
我爱你
I love you.
我也是
Aw, me too.
好了  够了
Okay, that's enough.
又一个用大麻解决的问题
And another problem solved by weed.
阿憨的妈妈  是时候该换人了
Hey, Han's mom. It's puff-puff-pass.
是我嗨昏头了
Am I super high
还是那个妓女真的在弹钢琴啊
or is that whore playing the piano?